{
    "subject": "resource/Tony_Benneworth",
    "predicate": "property/year",
    "object": "1971",
    "human_readable": "Tony Benneworth was born in 1971.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9720465540885925,
            "question": "If Tony Benneworth was born in 1971, what age would he be now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9242557287216187,
            "question": "When was Tony Benneworth born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8990731835365295,
            "question": "In what year was Tony Benneworth born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8159899115562439,
            "question": "What decade was Tony Benneworth born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8089888095855713,
            "question": "What significant historical events occurred during the year Tony Benneworth was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775171160697937,
            "question": "What is Tony Benneworth's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6423154473304749,
            "question": "How old is Tony Benneworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49221086502075195,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any notable people who were also born in 1971?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45572003722190857,
            "question": "What can you infer about Tony Benneworth's life based on his birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43871206045150757,
            "question": "Is Tony Benneworth a Millennial?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tony Benneworth was born in 1971.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4883_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you infer about Tony Benneworth's life based on his birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4883_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any notable people who were also born in 1971?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4883_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Tony Benneworth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4883_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4883_45.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents contain information about Tony Benneworth's birthdate, which is December 12, 1950, not 1971. This contradicts the statement \"Tony Benneworth was born in 1971.\" Therefore, the triple is incorrect according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Tony Benneworth's birth date as December 12, 1950. Therefore, the statement that he was born in 1971 is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}